[
	{ 
		"quizId": 1,
		"quiz": [
			{
				"question": "Who is Prime Minister of the United Kingdom?",
				"choices": ["David Cameron", "Gordon Brown", "Winston Churchill", "Tony Blair"], 
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "Who is the President of the United States?",
				"choices": ["2 Chainz", "Barack Obama", "An ostrich"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Who holds the button?",
				"choices": ["It's a cardigan button", "Trevor"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Here's a freeby",
				"choices": ["Select this to earn a FREE point"],
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "How many acorns in tree with three acorns, twelve leaves, twenty-five branches, sixty-five legumes?",
				"choices": ["One or two", "Acorn", "Peanut is a legume", "Acorns", "Demons"],
				"correctAnswer":3
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"quizId": 2,
		"quiz": [
			{
				"question": "Who is holding a small dog at this very moment?",
				"choices": ["David Cameron", "Gordon Brown", "Winston Churchill", "Tony Blair"], 
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "Who has been the lowest below sea level?",
				"choices": ["2 Chainz", "Barack Obama", "An ostrich"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Who holds the button?",
				"choices": ["It's a cardigan button", "Lue"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Here's a freeby",
				"choices": ["Select this to earn a FREE point"],
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "How many acorns in tree with three acorns, twelve leaves, twenty-five branches, sixty-five legumes?",
				"choices": ["One or two", "Acorn", "Peanut is a legume", "Acorns", "Demons"],
				"correctAnswer":3
			}
		]
	},
	{ 
		"quizId": 3,
		"quiz": [
			{
				"question": "Shump?",
				"choices": ["David Cameron", "Gordon Brown", "Winston Churchill", "Tony Blair"], 
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "Who is the President of the United States?",
				"choices": ["2 Chainz", "Barack Obama", "An ostrich"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Who holds the button?",
				"choices": ["It's a cardigan button", "Trevor"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Here's a freeby",
				"choices": ["Select this to earn a FREE point"],
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "How many acorns in tree with three acorns, twelve leaves, twenty-five branches, sixty-five legumes?",
				"choices": ["One or two", "Acorn", "Peanut is a legume", "Acorns", "Demons"],
				"correctAnswer":3
			}
		]
	},
	{ 
		"quizId": 4,
		"quiz": [
			{
				"question": "What's a better cat name?",
				"choices": ["Lumpy Lue", "Walter", "Simple Sally", "JJ Juicy"], 
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "Who is not the President of the United States?",
				"choices": ["2 Chainz", "Barack Obama", "An ostrich"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Who holds the button?",
				"choices": ["It's a cardigan button", "Trevor"],
				"correctAnswer":1
			},
			{
				"question": "Here's a freeby",
				"choices": ["Select this to earn a FREE point"],
				"correctAnswer":0
			},
			{
				"question": "How many acorns in tree with three acorns, twelve leaves, twenty-five branches, sixty-five legumes?",
				"choices": ["One or two", "Acorn", "Peanut is a legume", "Acorns", "Demons"],
				"correctAnswer":3
			}
		]
	}
]